# **Andrea Reyes**

# Andrea Margaret Sojuaco Garcia Reyes ( Dre )

702-859-8070

amgreyes23@gmail.com

\_

# Objective/Skills

I would like to work and grow with a company where knowledge and new skills can be acquired. I would like to further the skills and knowledge I already Have and expand my horizons

17 years of hospitality experience ranging from banquet serving to customer service. I have worked with Microsoft office programs, 10 key, cash register, Micros and Open Table.

\_

# **Experience**

#### October 2019- January 2020

**CSR-Sitel** 

Las Vegas,NV

Customer Service Call Center for costco.com. Help member with orders returns.

#### March 2019-Present

Cabana Server , Mandalay Bay

Las Vegas,NV

Customer service, open and close pool cabana. Serving all cabanas for the Mandalay Pool.

#### August 2018- February 2019

Security Officer, Palms

Las Vegas , NV

Provide service and security for Guest. Customer Service. Security for pool casino floor hotel towers inside outside grounds and concerts and special events

### August 2009- June 2018

Bartender, Server

Lagasse Stadium

Las Vegas, NV

Serving food and drinks to guest in a fast paced sports book and restaurant. Lead server for full restaurant buyouts serving up too as many as 1,300 guests.

#### December 2007- August 2009

Palazzo Sports Book

Las Vegas, NV

Serving food and making drinks for guests in a very fast paced environment with high table turnover.

.

### **Education**

# CSN/ Business

In progress

Eldorado HS / Diploma

Graduated 1999

**Awards** 

Worlds Greatest Mom.

## REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST